We at least survived one day.
We're not going home today.
Let's survive tomorrow as well.
- Let's survive tomorrow as well.
- Right.
- It's so...
- Let's do our best tomorrow...
- and survive the next day as well.
- Okay.
Even if we're just living day to day,
- staying alive is what matters.
- That's right.
Did the other teams
come to submit their lives?
Is Team Red submitting first?
- Oh, okay.
- So it shows like that...
when it's being used.
- They were quick.
- Right.
Please check the contents
of the central box...
and assign lives
to the residents of your choice.
(Life Submission for Day 1)
(Maillard)
(All members of Team Red survived.)
Your life submission is complete.
You may now leave.
I was actually considering it earlier.
(Maillard, cooking YouTuber)
I could kill the other members
if I wanted to.
Under the current rules,
if only one member is left on a team,
they no longer need any life.
The leader can always end up on their own.
But I don't think
there are only advantages to that.
It's still the first day,
and I don't know what more is out there.
And making that decision
could really isolate me,
so I didn't sabotage it.
I considered it a little.
- How many bathrooms are there?
- Two.
- That wouldn't take long then.
- How nice.
How many do you have?
- Three?
- We have three.
Well done.
Congratulations on surviving today.
Let's see each other for a long time.
The leader might not submit all the lives.
- You'd be dead then.
- That's so mean.
The leader could really choose
not to submit all of them.
I'll be the one killing everyone?
Goodness.
But to be able to come up
with that idea...
makes them different from me.
- Of course. You're a White.
- It didn't even cross my mind.
They're good at coming up
with cruel ideas.
Right. I guess you can see it
when you go in. The names and all.
I guess so.
Please check the contents
of the central box...
and assign lives
to the residents of your choice.
This really holds our lives.
(Life Submission for Day 1: Genie)
There.
A fake.
Let's ace the games tomorrow.
Go!
Your life submission is complete.
(All members of Team Blue survived.)
I didn't think much about it today.
Honestly, there's no merit.
If I get rid of the members today,
our team would lack in numbers.
But really, at that moment...
I thought, "I should really
keep my position as the leader."
It'll be over if the leader
doesn't place the life in my slot.
That's somehow more powerful...
than having an exemption card.
The leader can decide...
whether or not to keep someone alive...
during the submission.
So I thought being a leader...
was quite important.
More than the perks of being a leader,
I felt a responsibility
to take care of my team.
I didn't think that was a privilege.
Leia,
Luna,
Paul, Boss,
Siseon, and Hamlet.
Let's survive.
Your life submission is complete.
We all survived!
- Well done.
- This is fun.
I think becoming a leader
on the first day was a good decision...
because I got to experience such things.
It's quite fun to submit the resources.
- Really?
- Submitting the diamonds and all.
(Morning of Day 2)
Would you like a cup of coffee?
(Dormitory for White)
- You said you needed a caffeine fix.
- Right.
- Okay.
- I should, right?
It smells so nice.
The coffee smells nice.
- Have some of this.
- Okay.
- We have to work.
- Right.
We can't be sure if we'll be able
to buy lunch this afternoon.
Right. This could be our last meal.
They'll give us food, at least.
- Thank you for the coffee.
- Thank you.
You can have that.
I didn't have breakfast.
Inflation doesn't just affect the economy.
It affects our dopamine levels
and appetite too.
If we get into the habit
of eating like this,
we're going to lose it later on...
when the snack bar closes
or we run out of money.
So I wanted to get used to it.
(Dormitory for Red)
I wonder what we'll be producing.
Since there are many days to get through,
there'll obviously be things like quizzes.
I hope we're not going to that greenhouse.
Right.
- Start producing.
- In the real way.
Credits will be awarded
based on the weight...
of what you produce.
Just off the top of your head,
do you think Team Blue will give out
more than ten lives?
They should. We're 13 people.
They should distribute at least ten...
for us to survive the remaining days.
- Right?
- Yes.
In the worst case, we might all be
heading home the day after tomorrow.
That's the worst scenario.
Right. If they keep the lives.
Then, should we collect lives on our own?
Yes. We'll check out their stance today,
and if they're not willing to budge,
we'll just have to work hard tomorrow...
and find a way to get some lives.
(Dormitory for Blue)
I think giving out the lives...
one-for-one yesterday didn't make sense.
There wouldn't be so many lives.
It couldn't be helped since
we were feeling things out yesterday.
Team Red can still take it easy
at least for today.
Team White is the one without lives.
Team White will just live for today.
They're barely getting by.
Either way, at least through today,
they pretty much have to trade with us.
We went for it yesterday, so today...
- We have to play it safe today.
- At least...
We should secure the three lives
we're going to take first...
We might earn more. If we earn more...
For example, if we end up
with more than three,
we could sell those.
Right.
Also, I think...
we should pretend we're not making much.
Act like we don't have so many lives.
- Right.
- That way...
- That way, Team White...
- We can negotiate a higher price.
There's definitely going to come
a day when the lives become worthless.
Right.
Before they become worthless,
- we need to sell them for a high price...
- Right.
around the middle of the game.
But we really don't know what to expect
from Team White's money issuance.
It's a big unknown.
- Because...
- It's not fair.
They can't issue them
right after we've made our deal.
- That shouldn't happen.
- Right.
Our team's survival
is pretty much secured,
so I should start going
after some prize money.
But since Team White has complete control
over the diamonds,
I was really wondering
how they're going to issue them...
and how the whole system is going to work.
You have to keep...
whoever has a monopoly in check.
We should talk about that well...
- in advance, right?
- Right.
I was thinking maybe we should try
working with the other teams.
It's true that we need
to issue currency now...
to keep things flowing smoothly.
Right now, each diamond
is worth 1,000 dollars, and that's huge.
So we need to issue currency.
But if we start
issuing currency recklessly,
the other teams could get suspicious...
and we could also start
mistrusting each other.
We can tell them that and say,
"We'll make an announcement
like the Bank of Korea."
In return, we'll ask them to guarantee
our survival...
and our credits,
which give us the right to work.
I think we should make our deal
based on the fact...
that we work most efficiently
when all six of us are working together.
I think issuing too many diamonds...
could cause some confusion.
So we're trying to make sure
we communicate that well...
to the other teams in advance,
so we can rebuild trust...
without causing too much disruption
to prices.
That's what we're aiming for.
If we issued too much,
it could break the trust
between the teams.
Since we needed to secure enough lives,
it was more important to show
that we can be trusted.
If they don't agree with this,
we could say, "We'll increase
the amount of currency in circulation..."
"beyond a certain limit
and not say anything."
I think that could be our greatest weapon.
That's our greatest and only weapon.
It's our only weapon.
How transparent...
are we talking about?
We'll keep the amount
of currency we issue...
- within a certain limit.
- For example, we'll increase...
- the money supply by 10 percent a day.
- We'll increase it by 10 percent.
- We'll do that.
- That much.
Do you want us to set a rule like that?
- And announce it to them?
- We'll announce it to them.
But one thing we absolutely
shouldn't tell them...
- is that there's a limit.
- Right.
(Last night)
Everyone.
It's written here that we can issue...
up to 200 additional diamonds once a day.
- Once per person.
- Once a day?
- Once a day.
Starting on Day Two,
Team White can submit...
the provided diamond issuance voucher...
during Community Center hours...
and issue up to 200 additional diamonds...
once per day.
No credits are required
to issue additional diamonds.
That means we can't make
the value of the currency drop so much...
- The voucher...
- as we get further into the game.
- Because we can issue...
- That's right.
- only up to 200 diamonds per day.
- Right.
- We can only make it drop at first.
It won't fall so much from the next day.
We also don't need to put...
- a lot into circulation early on.
- That's right.
If we keep the money supply low
at the beginning...
and increase it little by little,
then if we suddenly issue
200 a day right at the end,
the value is going to drop by almost half.
We should make use of that.
- That's right.
- Yes.
What percentage should we promise
to increase it by in the beginning?
So I think...
- By ten percent?
- we should check the prices first.
- The prices.
- We should check...
the current market prices.
- Right. The prices...
- How much Black is selling them for.
We also need to check
how many lives and credits...
- we can actually produce.
- That's right.
That's right.
We're going to have lunch
after the game, right?
Yes. It will be lunchtime.
We should buy it from Vector.
I think if we stay...
on good terms with Vector,
we could get a lot of information
for free.
But Vector's friendliness
could also be calculated.
- I think he's that kind of character.
- That's possible.
Just accumulating a lot of diamonds
is a little too one-dimensional.
I feel like there's something more to it.
Right.
What could that be?
It's not about collecting many diamonds.
Maillard is certain
that it's not about collecting diamonds.
No one did a better job of winning
people over yesterday than Vector.
He really won everyone over yesterday.
He's the only person
who went around to every team...
and won people over.
Honestly, I think whoever gets Vector
on their side...
has the biggest advantage.
There are six members here,
- Right.
- and it doesn't feel like...
we've completely...
- clicked with the three Team Red members.
- Exactly.
To succeed in winning over Team Red,
we must use this very person.
- True.
- Right?
- He's sly.
- Yes.
- Very.
- He is.
- He's sly.
- Right?
(The Community 2: Invisible Hand)
(2: When We Want the Same Thing)
Day Two has begun.
Team leaders can now be changed...
at the Community Center.
Discuss whether to reappoint
the current leader.
What matters is whether anyone wants...
- to become the leader.
- True.
If anyone wants to become the leader,
please speak up.
Was there any benefit to being the leader?
- Being one feels good?
- No.
- Maybe this much?
- This badge.
- I see, so it's the badge.
Do you want to be one?
No, I'm fine.
How about we have her serve again?
I prefer chirping away as just a member.
It seems like it.
I support Luna.
- Same here.
- I support her.
- Shall we show off our unity?
- Okay.
(Team White's leader
has been reappointed.)
- Great.
- Good.
How about reappointing him?
I totally agree with that.
Changing our leader
didn't even cross my mind...
because Maillard made trades yesterday
very adamantly.
So, I thought he should continue
being the leader...
and didn't have a second thought about it.
- Maillard.
- Yes?
- I love you being the leader.
- Totally.
I know, right? It's reassuring.
However,
neither the power...
nor the role of the leader
has been revealed completely.
That feeling of holding
the power of life and death...
when submitting the life at night is...
Should I suggest taking turns
as the leader?
But bringing it up right now
in this situation...
might arouse unnecessary suspicions.
I didn't have any reason.
Who wants to be the leader today?
- Salt.
- Me today?
- Go ahead.
- Yes.
All right, I'll be the leader today.
- Decided.
(Team Blue's leader: Salt)
Our team decided to take turns,
so it wasn't a matter of satisfaction
and whatnot.
I like this system.
At this rate,
we'll just keep taking turns.
I wasn't sure if it was efficient.
I'm thinking of taking the role.
We need to head to the Community Center.
- Is that where we announce the leader?
- Yes.
- I'm off.
- Bye.
(Team Red's Day 2 leader: Maillard)
(Team White's Day 2 leader: Luna)
(Team Black's Day 2 leader: Vector)
Collect the Day Two schedule...
from the central box.
(Community Center)
Hi.
- Hi.
Are you reappointing the leader?
- No, we're changing.
- No, ours change every day.
- Turns.
- Our plan is to take turns.
- We're taking turns.
- Could we...
- talk outside for a minute?
- Sure. Got it.
If you wish to change your leader,
please state the name of the new leader.
We'd like to change the leader to Salt.
The new leader is to collect
the instructions from the central box.
Here are some instructions.
- Production rules.
Starting Day Two, every team can earn...
lives or credits
through productive activities.
Submit one credit at the production site,
and you will receive
ten production questions per day.
If you want a hint,
A hint, please.
an additional credit is required.
If you wish to retry
after an incorrect answer,
We'd like to retry.
you must also pay an additional credit.
During production activities,
the amount of resources...
each team can receive varies.
"If Team White chooses to produce
lives or credits,"
"one life or credit is produced
for every three correct answers."
"If the team answers
all ten questions correctly,"
"they will produce
a total of five lives or credits."
- Three questions.
- One per three questions.
The return is terrible.
It's really terrible.
This is bad.
Looking at the ratio, it's 3-to-1.
We have to solve 3 just to get 1,
and the questions
definitely won't be easy.
If we...
do really well, maybe we can get three?
Wouldn't getting two be enough
to break even?
It's very upsetting and unreasonable.
The production efficiency is way too low.
Is such a low production efficiency
even right with this many people?
If only we could receive
a bit more generosity, you know?
Do you think it's the same
for the other teams?
The amount must be different
for each team.
- Credits? Right.
- For example,
get 1 question right,
and that team gets 1 resource right away.
Could the ratio be 3-to-1 for us
and 1-to-1 for them?
Maybe.
"If Team Blue chooses to produce lives,"
- "one life is produced..."
- We've got...
- "for every correct answer."
- a great deal.
"If the team chooses to produce credits,"
"one credit is produced
for every three correct answers."
The 3-to-1 ratio was correct.
It's only reasonable for us
to produce lives.
- Exactly.
- I told you.
- The ratio of lives can't be 1-to-1.
- But...
Since yesterday, I kept saying...
how one credit could not be
the same as one life.
Even at the lowest,
it's one credit per team,
which gets you a minimum ratio of 3-to-1.
Credits were mentioned as opportunities.
The opportunity must be to earn lives.
If you think about it logically,
such a ratio is impossible.
Either way, we traded five lives.
One credit is worth...
a huge number of lives.
We really got the short end of the stick.
There is a limited total supply of lives
that can be produced.
This supply is shared across
the entire Community Town,
so even if multiple teams
produce lives independently,
they are all deducted
from the same shared pool.
(Total life supply)
Goodness.
If the life supply holds a total of 10,
the other team produces 5,
and we produce 3, only 2 are left.
That's tough.
- The production rules are absurd.
- I see.
The ratio is hard to believe.
Get 1 question right,
and we get 3 credits.
Get 3 questions right, and we get 1 life.
One per three answers?
Get 6 right, and we'd get 2 lives.
Right now...
Now that I'm looking at it,
- the ratio is 9-to-1.
- You're right.
Right? It's 9-to-1.
This ratio is crazy.
It's close to the 10-to-1 ratio
we had guessed.
- Is that so?
- Yes, it's 9-to-1.
- Oh, my.
- Exactly.
- In short, we use...
- Yes?
one credit to get ten questions...
- and use about 5 to 6 credits...
- Yes?
- for the hint or to retry.
- Right.
We could earn about 7 credits and 2 lives.
Gosh, the ratio is out of this world.
Or we could use 7 credits
and earn 21 credits.
That feels right.
- All done?
- Hi.
Why do you look shocked?
- It's nothing.
- There's so much information,
- so my brain isn't working.
- Is that so?
Well...
- If I'm being completely honest...
- Yes?
- You don't have any lives, do you?
- I need lives.
Right.
(During last night's life submission)
(1 life is needed to run the supermarket
for a day.)
(Vector submits the 1 life he had.)
To run it the next day...
How do I get a life?
But we can't trade.
So I did a lot of thinking yesterday.
I had zero lives today.
I thought long and hard about
how to earn lives.
No matter how much I read the rule book,
I couldn't trade for lives or credits.
I'd either have to be handed some over...
or trade in a black market
outside the law.
Since I can't trade for lives,
I have to earn them another way.
So I'm going to create a black market.
Is that possible?
I don't know.
I'm just going to give it a shot.
- What? A shot?
- Here's what I can offer.
Give me a life, and in return,
I will provide
whatever food you want for two days.
If we agree to it...
Under the assumption that
we have enough food,
there's no benefit for us.
Shouldn't we get a certain percentage
of the sales revenue?
That way, we'd actually come out ahead.
Do you not need food?
It's not that necessary at the moment.
- We can starve for hours.
- Exactly.
- Starve for hours?
- I've been on a diet for a long time.
- Coincidentally...
- I've been needing to go on a diet.
I didn't see this coming.
But even we don't know
how many lives we can produce.
We'll find out only after
this production activity is over.
We could talk about this again
after seeing how many we can produce...
- and whether there's room to adjust...
- True.
the percentage.
- But...
- Frankly, food isn't important to us.
- But we've talked about wanting...
- Yes?
to get along with you.
It really was a topic this morning.
It wasn't something we really needed.
But it was a step needed to form...
a relationship with Black,
so we were okay with it for that purpose.
For now...
I'll take it that
you're willing to make a deal.
- Yes.
- That's for sure.
Let's leave it at this.
We'll have the right to...
- first distribution.
- Okay.
Please save me.
That depends on the deal we make.
- For sure.
- What a power trip.
- We'll think about it.
- Got it.
- For now, take care.
- Take care.
- That was cute, Pitou.
- Really.
With a girly dress on, Pitou...
- She's giving off cool gangster vibes.
- Right?
- She's full of surprises.
- How much we can produce...
- A woman full of surprises.
- is still a mystery.
It's something to think about.
We really need to think things through,
as some things are still unknown to us.
- For now...
- For now, we'll see how things unfold.
- Let's read that first.
- Let's open this.
- Let's read it thoroughly.
- Goodness.
Team Blue's skill is
Right to Access Information.
Starting today,
teams can develop new skills...
alongside their production activities.
Each team can solve
the assigned development questions...
to acquire specialized skills.
"You can access information
such as the quantity of one resource..."
"or the current value of a diamond."
This will play a big role
in the latter half.
Do we need a life to check it?
Team Blue's skill is
Right to Access Information.
We need to use one life...
to check the information.
There may be times when the information...
is important enough
to justify using up a life,
even if it isn't an urgent matter
right now.
- This...
- We need to hoard...
as many lives as possible.
- We do.
- If that's true,
the credit deal yesterday was a good move.
We have to use those credits...
- and exchange them for lives.
- Right.
Look.
"If Team Black solves
another team's development question..."
"first..."
All development questions
are also provided to Team Black.
If Team Black solves
another team's development question first,
that team must purchase the skill...
from Team Black to use it.
The purchase price will be determined
through negotiation and paid in diamonds.
However,
Team Black cannot use any skills...
belonging to other teams
that it has solved.
Black will devote himself
to solving our questions.
It's one of the mighty powers
that Black has.
He can access all kinds of information.
We could steal some of that power
from Black.
The current value
of one diamond may be critical,
so securing diamonds felt like
the right thing to do.
- "That day..."
- "That day,"
"we realized that even a country
could go bankrupt."
It's in here.
I recall something about bankruptcy
in here.
"From this point on,
once our country's culture and economy..."
"move past the stage of rapid growth
and enter a period of relaxed growth..."
What?
(Lock, Key)
Key and lock?
Isn't that a line from a movie?
You mean "Default?"
Something like...
- What does this mean?
- What's this about?
"Teams must solve..."
I can't even grasp an idea about it.
Such a question is a first in my life.
I have zero idea.
To acquire specialized skills
unique to each team,
teams must solve the development question
assigned to them.
Each team's development question...
consists of a key and a lock.
The key is a sentence...
describing a major economic event
recorded in history.
(1997 Asian Financial Crisis
IMF Bailout Request)
Using clues related to the event,
teams can uncover the secret sentence
hidden inside the lock.
These clues are hidden in books
placed in each team's accommodation.
("Market's Memory,"
"The Disappearing Spoon," "The Ghost Map")
Is this about the Asian Financial Crisis?
Is it in one of the books?
I think I recently read an article
in "Sisain."
I'm sure I brought it.
Nothing really came to my mind.
The others seemed...
very serious about solving the question.
But looking at it for long...
won't get me the answer.
Get it right, then good.
If not, it's fine.
- But if you look here,
- Yes?
- there's an even more shocking rule.
- Okay.
We can make bombs using ten credits.
- If we use ten credits to make a bomb,
- What?
we can get rid of a team's three lives.
An example would be taking away one day.
Team Red's specialized skill is
Bomb Manufacturing License.
By spending ten credits,
Team Red can manufacture one bomb.
If a bomb is used against a specific team,
three lives belonging to that team
will be destroyed.
- What?
- But to make the bombs,
we have to answer...
- the skill development questions.
- Right.
- Black received the same questions.
- Oh, dear.
If Black solves the questions first,
we have to buy the skill from him.
But Black is intelligent.
- We have to solve them fast.
- Okay.
Okay. R and D.
"That winter, the beautiful windmill..."
"suddenly exploded along with..."
(That winter, the beautiful windmill...)
(suddenly exploded along with
a massive bubble.)
Windmill? The windmill exploded.
(The development of the ten resources
and the settlement period...)
(are gradually approaching
their deadlines.)
What's this?
Gosh, the question was hard.
"That winter, the beautiful..."
Key and lock?
Vector must be...
really smart.
Even our team thought
it was a really tough question.
But if all three went to Vector...
and he solved them all,
he'd have...
a skill advantage over the other three
in negotiations.
"This guy isn't here to simply sell things
at the supermarket."
"He's a brainiac."
Those were what I thought.
Skill development?
"Team White's specialized skill is
the Digital Currency Issuance Authority."
"Currently, Team White can issue
an additional 200 diamonds..."
"once per day."
"Once skill development is completed,"
"the issuance limit for diamonds
will be removed,"
"and all diamonds will be converted
to digital currency."
"During Community Center operating hours,"
"digital diamonds can be issued
at the Center..."
"by submitting an issuance voucher,"
"with no limits on the amount
or number of issuances."
- Nice.
- Amazing.
- This feels unreal.
- We gained extreme power.
I thought of it
as a kind of nuclear missile.
Either everyone has to develop it,
or no one should be able to.
That was the only way to maintain peace.
Not answering is not even an option.
It's like a nuclear button.
I could kind of understand why...
many countries are trying to develop
nuclear weapons...
they can't even use.
The benefit is no joke.
- It's unbelievable.
- Isn't it what we wanted the most?
- Why did we fabricate the percentage?
- Cybermoney...
It's for that.
It'll become Bitcoin.
This isn't even Bitcoin.
It's just some junk coin.
A real, total junk coin.
- Let's look at it together.
- "Key."
"That Monday,
the tower built by desires..."
"came crashing down in silence."
"Lock."
"The production of essential food supplies
such as instant noodles and flour is..."
"directly linked to oil reserves..."
(Team White's skill development question)
- Sorry?
- What does this mean?
Isn't it nuclear?
I was like, "What does this mean?"
Why did the sentence stop midway?
It was difficult to the point of
making me wonder,
"Are they really expecting us
to solve this?"
I'm at a total loss.
"That Monday?"
Something about Monday
and the Tower of Babel.
("Curious Coffins and Riveting Rituals,"
"The Disappearing Spoon")
(Key, Lock)
("The Ghost Map," "Baekbeom Ilji,"
"The History of Money")
Couldn't the bubble be related to...
the bubble economy?
Something with economy.
The part about
exploding along with a bubble...
could have something to do with Bitcoin.
There's a reference to Bitcoin on page 17.
- Really?
- Yes.
This book keeps bringing up Bitcoin.
Yes.
- I think we're on the right track.
- What?
- Try it.
- Give me a second.
- But...
- There's no penalty even if you're wrong.
- I'm off.
- Does it have to be the leader?
- Maybe not.
- Anyone can go. You've already tried.
- I'll go this time.
- Okay.
- Think about it.
- I will.
- It's tough. Key and lock.
- Where have I seen it?
I think it's Black Monday.
- Black... Oh, right!
- Yes.
- Black Monday?
You know how,
- during the Great Depression,
- Yes?
the stock market was inflated
by people's greed...
- and then suddenly collapsed?
- Right.
- It's Monday. It must be Black Monday.
- "That Monday?"
- Yes.
- You're right.
Everyone is so smart.
- I think...
- Is the answer "yes" or "no?"
It could be "yes" or "no."
Should we give it a try?
It's not like we have to submit...
- a credit to answer or anything.
- No.
- The rest of it...
- I'm off.
- Okay.
- What is it?
- Is it directly related to...
(Dormitory for Black)
Gosh, there were three questions.
I carried them around,
trying to figure out...
what the answers could be.
If I could get all three answers,
I'd hit the jackpot.
(Each team takes on an answer.)
That is incorrect.
- Did you try?
- It was incorrect.
- Bitcoin was wrong, right?
- Yes.
Cryptocurrency?
Is it cryptocurrency?
The possibility of it being cryptocurrency
is 99 percent.
Go. Get going already.
Wasn't the lock cryptocurrency?
- Cryptocurrency, lock, cryptocurrency...
- How is it...
What happens if you add
cryptocurrency to Bitcoin?
You either go big or go home.
Rotate it. What happens?
It's not Bitcoin.
- Cryptocurrency.
- Ten.
Cryptocurrency?
(The skill development questions
are getting harder to crack.)
It was incorrect. We were wrong.
Answering it in one day won't be easy.
Well done, guys.
- It'd be best to solve it today.
- Right.
Let's keep thinking about it.
It's fine as long as we answer it
before Vector does.
I'm someone who imagines the worst.
Even if Vector gets the skills,
what matters is our cooperation with him.
- Right.
- It won't be a loss.
- We'll be fine.
- Correct.
Today's production activity
will begin shortly.
Residents,
please proceed to the production site
assigned to your team.
(White production site,
Red production site, Blue production site)
There are three production sites in total,
and each team will carry out
its production activities...
at a different site.
(White production site)
(Blue production site)
(Red production site)
What a cool place.
- Here?
- Interesting.
What's this place for?
I don't have a clue.
(The teams have arrived
at their production sites.)
I'm worried.
- What?
- I'm worried about what we'll have to do.
Welcome to the production site.
The production activity will last
three hours.
Three hours to answer ten questions?
Just how hard are they?
If we're getting three hours,
the questions must be hard for sure.
Let's leave after answering them
in 15 minutes.
- We're tired.
- Are you a genius?
I should've brought a calculator.
Before the production activity begins,
Team Blue will be informed of
the total life supply.
Total life supply.
(Team Blue can check the total life supply
at the production site.)
There are a total of...
(Total life supply)
fifty lives in the available supply.
Fifty?
That's not a lot.
We're just expected to die.
- Yes, someone has to die.
- Right?
As of Day Two,
there are 13 residents in Community Town.
Since no lives will be submitted
on the final day, Day Nine,
each person needs
a total of seven lives to survive...
until the end.
Therefore, including
Team Black's supermarket operations,
a total of 91 lives are needed...
for all residents to survive,
calculated as 13 people
multiplied by 7 lives each.
However, when we add up all the lives
currently held by the residents,
there are only 30.
Even if all 50 lives in the supply...
are successfully produced,
on the 8th day,
there will be 11 lives short,
and people will have to leave.
We discovered
that it's systematically impossible...
for all of us to survive.
I basically thought,
"What can you do about it?"
People will be forced out
before you know it.
This will be cutthroat.
I'm suddenly nervous.
Each group's production capacity
will vary.
Once you choose a resource to produce,
ring the bell and announce it.
Our best bet is to get
as many lives as possible...
- and strike deals.
- Exactly.
Lives.
Lives, please.
Team Blue has chosen "life,"
and one life will be produced
for each correct answer.
The number of lives we need...
- are 4.
- We need 4, at least.
- We'll set that as our goal for now.
- Sure.
Lives, please.
Team White has chosen "life,"
and 1 life will be produced
for every 3 correct answers.
Should you answer
all ten questions correctly,
you'll produce five lives.
If we get all ten questions...
We get two more lives.
(1 life per 3 correct answers,
5 lives for all 10 correct answers)
We have 18, right?
I bet both teams
have fewer than three credits.
They're going to be thirsty for more.
We'll produce credits.
Team Red has chosen "credit,"
and three credits will be produced
for every correct answer.
Here's the keyword
for today's production round.
There's a keyword.
Today's production round keyword...
is "mystery paper."
Mystery Paper is a game
where you identify something...
- through a series of images.
- It could be the same size.
Place one of your credits...
- in the credit box.
- Let's go.
(1 credit gives them 10 questions.)
Let's do this.
It's counting down.
- Go, team.
- Let's go.
Drop the question.
- I'm nervous.
- Question number one.
(Mystery Paper)
This is an LP record
made for a special purpose...
that was revealed in 1977.
What's the name of this LP record?
- What?
What was that?
An LP record made for a special purpose?
It was revealed in 1977.
Shouldn't we think of artists...
who were releasing albums in 1977?
Who comes to mind?
I'm drawing a blank even on that.
(What's the name of
the special-purpose LP record from 1977?)
Music?
- Can I take a closer look?
- Sure.
We were told to guess
based on what we see.
There must be a clue.
I think it's something from here.
This part has been covered up.
You're right. They whited it out.
This is what we have to guess.
The answer is what they covered up.
Planet?
The Sounds of...
United States of America, Planet...
We can agree it's an American artist.
- Revealed in 1977...
- This looks like Earth.
Right.
Right, that's Earth.
Wait, is that the moon?
Earth and the moon.
So couldn't it be...
Is it something that was first launched?
Maybe it's related to that.
That's not a field I know a lot about.
Is it related to something
that was launched into space?
Are you talking about Neil Armstrong...
and the first moon landing?
Even if that's the case,
what could be the name of this album?
Gosh, just kill me already.
- What?
- On the way there...
- In 1977...
- I know the answer.
It's "The Sounds of Earth."
It was sent to space.
In case an alien species
picks up this album,
sounds of Earth were recorded on it.
The Sounds of...
- Earth?
- Earth.
- That's it.
- That should be it.
They covered the last word.
- Right.
- I see.
- "The Sounds of Earth."
- Let's try that.
- Shall we?
- Yes, let's do it.
"The Sounds of Earth."
That is correct.
(Team Red gets 1 question right.)
"Hey, I know this one."
That's what I immediately thought.
I figured today's production round...
might not be so difficult.
In less than a minute, he spoke up...
and said he knew the answer.
I was happy...
to have him on my team.
I have a good feeling about today.
Thanks for that.
That was perfect.
Just perfect.
The Voyager Golden Record.
("The Sounds of Earth" is an LP
included aboard the Voyager spacecraft.)
(It features nature sounds, music,
55 languages, and images.)
- Music...
- That's the album included...
aboard the Voyager spacecraft.
The Golden Record.
From what I recall,
it features greetings...
in languages from all around the world.
Music too, actually.
Songs by the Beatles
failed to make the cut.
Siseon knew exactly what it was.
He was aware of the title...
and what was included on the LP.
The answer is "The Sounds of Earth."
(Team White gives the same answer.)
That is correct.
(Team White gets 1 question right.)
- Nice.
- No way.
- That's it.
- That's insane.
I like watching science YouTubers.
You sure know a lot.
Thank you.
I pulled my weight enough today
that I'll sleep well tonight.
Things just started getting fun,
and my heart began to race.
- Not French, right?
- I wonder who the artist is.
Planet...
Hold on. Planet and Earth.
Is it something like "blue?"
Wouldn't it be too easy?
The title would then be
"The Sounds of Earth."
Rather than Earth...
Planet? Earth makes it sound weird.
I've been relying on AI too much.
I was disappointed in myself
for being so dumb.
I was embarrassed to reveal
that I don't read much,
but it was a hard question to answer.
It may be a record,
but I don't think it's by
an actual artist.
It makes more sense
that it was a signal for the launch,
or perhaps a collection of those sounds.
That could be it.
The sounds of Earth
meant for aliens to find?
Yes, that's it!
I read it somewhere. That's the answer.
- Should we just go with Earth?
- Let's go with Earth.
- Let's think about it some more.
- We can pass, right?
If we're not going to bother
asking for a hint,
let's just go with Earth.
Let's do it.
"The Sounds of Earth."
That is correct.
(Team Blue gets 1 question right.)
No way. I can't believe we got it.
Seriously. No way.
I've got all the dopamine
I need for today.
Who needs food to be full, right?
- Next question, please.
- Hit us with the next question.
Next question.
(Next question)
"The following image shows
a prehistoric rock..."
"registered
as a UNESCO World Heritage site."
"In which city
was this petroglyph discovered?"
Prehistoric?
Darn.
A prehistoric rock?
A city?
In Korea?
- Isn't it in Korea?
- I see a lot of animals.
- Those are whales.
- Aren't they fish?
Yes, whales.
Most of them are marine animals.
I see turtles.
- Which country is it in?
- I even see some deer.
- Isn't that a person?
- I see a person's face.
The city it was discovered in?
The city and not the country?
Which city can you find those animals in?
I think it's a city overseas.
I'm strongly leaning
towards Spain or Portugal.
- But it's not...
- It's a city.
Yes, it's a city, so I'm completely lost.
I don't think it's from Korea.
The petroglyph details don't seem Korean.
- They look more African to me.
- I agree.
Since it's from a prehistoric age,
the details might not hugely differ...
from country to country.
- So it could be Korean?
- Yes.
Have you heard
about a prehistoric rock in Korea...
being named a UNESCO World Heritage site?
- There are a lot more than you think.
- Really?
The only one I can think of...
is the one in Ulju-gun.
- That's a great place.
- Ulju.
- Ulju?
- Yes.
Jeju Island?
That's a pretty good guess.
Ulsanbawi is Korea's most famous rock.
It's not in Ulsan, but still.
- Didn't you say you're from Ulsan?
- Yes.
Wouldn't you have
picked up on something...
- since you lived there?
- There aren't any big rocks in Ulsan.
- Ulsanbawi isn't in Ulsan.
- That's right.
Ulsanbawi is on Mount Seorak.
A prehistoric rock?
If I'm not overstepping,
- may I answer the question?
- Seriously?
- Yes.
- What's gotten into you?
- It's where my university is located.
- Right.
- Ulsan.
- Sure.
Ulsan is the city of whales.
Just so you know,
Ulsan is known for its whales.
That's the Bangudae Petroglyphs in Ulsan.
I think I remember seeing
that it was listed...
as a UNESCO World Heritage site.
Ulsan is a small city,
so I feel like I would've heard
if it had been listed...
as a heritage site.
The answer is Ulsan.
Jeju.
Ulju-gun?
That is correct.
(Correct)
- I'm over the moon!
- That's great.
I'm so happy right now.
What? Ulsan was the right answer!
- Sorry about that.
- Are you kidding me?
(It became a UNESCO World Heritage site
in July 2025.)
I knew I was onto something.
- Seriously?
- Look here.
Ms. Ulsan, really?
Hold on a second.
- Ms. Ulsan, really?
- No wonder.
Ulsan's famous for its whales.
Look here.
I didn't guess Ulsan right,
even though it's my hometown.
I'm getting a lot of grief because of it.
I won't ever say I'm from Ulsan again.
Sorry about that.
That is correct.
(Correct)
(Donkey gives his team
two correct answers in a row.)
Are you kidding me?
- Is he a spy?
- What's with him?
He could be a spy,
here to make our lives...
- difficult tomorrow.
- That's possible.
(Giving correct answers
makes him suspicious.)
Seriously. How did you know
it was in Ulsan?
What I thought at the time?
"Is Donkey a spy?"
It just didn't seem possible.
Did he have all the answers?
That's just how good he was.
At that moment,
I couldn't help doubting him.
Seriously.
He got two correct answers back-to-back.
- Are you from Ulsan?
- Beats me.
- Next question.
- Sounds good.
This is a 19th-century Korean map
currently housed...
at the French National Library.
(It's the first map to spell Seoul
in the Roman alphabet.)
Who drew it?
That says Seoul,
but what's that on its side?
Gyeonggi Province?
Hold on.
Isn't that Dokdo?
The map even includes Dokdo.
- Was the cartographer Korean?
- I think he was Korean.
Since everything is written
in the Roman alphabet,
there's a good chance
the cartographer was a foreigner.
Hamel?
- Hamel?
- "Hamel's Journal."
Hamel.
That is incorrect.
(Incorrect)
Could it be Columbia
or something like that?
- Columbia?
- Columbia...
Is that right? Wait, is it Columbus?
Columbia?
Are you kidding me?
Nobody realized
that what you said was wrong.
Columbus, it is.
Columbus...
Columbus.
That is incorrect.
Can you tell us the answer?
- I really want to know.
- Please tell us the answer.
From the 19th century.
- Should we get the hint?
- Yes.
Why don't we get a hint?
We'll take a hint.
Please insert a credit in the credit box.
Here's your hint.
(Here's your hint.)
The hint for question three.
"On the stained glass of Barcelona's
Basilica of the Sagrada Familia,"
"the names of martyred saints from
around the world are written."
Martyred saints?
Isn't there a famous person from Korea?
That person is even listed
at the Roman Curia.
There's a statue of this person.
- The last name is Kim.
- Right. It's Kim.
It's A. Kim.
Is there a biblical name
that starts with A?
- Andrea.
- Oh, Andrea!
I think Andrea is right. But...
- There should be a Korean name.
- The Korean name...
Should we say it's Andrea Kim
and insist that's right?
It's not exactly wrong.
Here's our answer.
We will go with Andrea Kim.
That is correct.
Right! Priest Kim Tae Gon.
(Answer: Priest Andrea Kim Tae Gon)
(Priest Kim Tae Gon created
the Carte de la Coree in 1845.)
(It's the first map to mark
Korea's capital as Seoul.)
(It was an important map that displayed
Korea's location to the West...)
(along with the Romanized version
of Woosando, the old name of Dokdo.)
What is this?
As soon as I heard Andrea,
it fit perfectly with A. Kim.
That was how I figured it out.
- Here's the next question.
- Gosh, I feel so happy.
(This was an actual job in the UK
from the 17th to 20th century.)
"This was an actual job in the UK."
(What is the role of the man
wearing green?)
That looks like a casket.
It looks like they're eating something...
on top of the corpse.
Are those fruit?
- Potatoes?
- A mortician?
There are morticians now.
- That must not be it.
- There are still morticians.
The man is kneeling...
- as if he's proposing.
- Right.
Is it like a spiritual wedding?
- The woman is wearing a wedding dress.
- Right.
- A medium?
- I think medium sounds right...
as it's a job.
Medium.
That is incorrect.
We didn't get it.
I think this one is worth
checking the hint.
We have the confidence to answer
everything with the hint.
We'll check the hint.
Please insert one credit
into the credit box.
(Team Red's Credit Usage,
Total 3: 1 question, 2 hints)
Here's your hint.
"The woman is passing the bread
and drink over the corpse."
- "The man ate it."
Isn't it something like this?
This is done in Hong Kong.
Let's say something bad happened to me.
I throw a coin on the street.
When someone passing by picks that up,
my bad luck moves to that person.
- There's this kind of superstition.
- Right.
If the one who is dead is guilty of a sin,
this man takes the guilt instead...
after eating the food.
There's a child.
- Seeing the child hold the casket,
- Could it be the child's father?
it might be the child's father.
An acting chief mourner?
We'll go with acting chief mourner.
That is incorrect.
The one who takes away
the misfortune of the deceased.
- That is correct.
- Gosh, that was it.
(Answer: Sin-eater)
- You were spot on.
- Right.
She's the one from
The University of Hong Kong.
Exactly.
The one who eats food
instead of the deceased.
- The guilt of the deceased is carried.
- I see.
The guilt is carried?
We weren't able to reach guilt.
Doesn't the Sin Eater...
- appear in Final Fantasy X?
- Really?
- Right. The sin-eater.
- Gosh.
- We didn't get it.
- Here's the next question.
"A print that satirized a specific job."
"The job of the ones in the drawing..."
"is currently split up
as two different jobs in modern times."
A dentist! They're pulling out his teeth.
They're holding up a mirror
while cutting hair.
- It's a barber.
- Right.
But in the top left,
it looks like they're working on the leg.
A doctor? A doctor and nurse?
I remember hearing that a hairdresser
used to act as a doctor.
You've all seen the symbol
of a barber, right?
The thing that turns
with white, red, and blue.
The blue and red represent...
the veins and arteries.
Should we go with surgeon?
They aren't internists.
Surgeon and hairdresser!
Barber and surgeon.
Surgeon and barber.
- That is correct.
- We got it.
Here's the next question.
It's from 1854. London's Soho area.
It's a residence.
The pump is highlighted in yellow.
All I can think of is the Black Death.
(Which disease did John Snow track...)
(with the map of London's Soho residence
in 1854?)
I think it's cholera, everyone.
Cholera spread through the water...
from the water pipes.
Didn't cholera spread through water?
- Wait.
We read about this!
- This was in the book.
- We read about this!
(This morning)
("The Ghost Map")
- The answer is cholera.
- Cholera.
That is correct.
- Hey!
- Gosh!
- That was so sexy!
- Yes!
We read about this
in the book of diseases!
- We read about it in the morning!
- Right.
- I read diligently.
Here's the next question.
"This is a sketch made..."
"by a scientist in 1837."
- Is it Einstein?
- Special relativity.
- The theory of evolution!
- What?
- The theory of evolution?
- Darwin's theory of evolution.
The picture of the tree branching out...
is a huge picture of the Tree of Life.
I think it's the theory of evolution.
"On the Origin of Species,"
theory of evolution.
I think we can get it right with the hint.
- Let's pay.
- Okay.
- It's not that bad.
See? It's the theory of evolution.
- Theory of evolution.
That is correct.
- Thank you.
- It was an easy question.
It's the Tree of Life.
- I feel so embarrassed.
- Special relativity.
That is incorrect.
- Too bad.
Here's the next question.
(This is the experiment note
written by Grace Hopper,)
(a female scientist of the US.
Which word started being used by this?)
Grace Hopper was really famous.
What is that? Is that a bug?
- A bug? That's a bug!
- Right.
I was thinking of Morse code
because of "moth."
Bug? Oh, right!
- A bug went in the computer.
- Right.
- Right. There's that story.
- That was how "bug" was used.
That was how it started being called
a "bug."
Bug.
Morse code.
That is correct.
- Thank you.
- What's with us?
That is incorrect.
- I didn't expect to get it right.
- Here's the next question.
I don't know.
"What hath God wrought?"
The name of this signal?
Isn't it Morse code this time?
- Morse code?
- Isn't it Morse code?
I think it's Morse code.
O is three dots.
W is three long lines.
Dot... It's Morse code.
- But...
- But it's too...
- That might be too easy.
- It's like SOS.
Right. The answer might be Morse code...
or a separate name for this.
- A separate name?
- Right.
We should clear things up
by checking the hint.
- Shall we check the hint?
- Since we have a lot?
Please insert one credit
into the credit box.
"It was used during the first experimental
long-distance telegraph line..."
"from Washington, D.C to Baltimore
in 1844."
Isn't it really Morse code?
I think I've read about this
from a biography.
Something Way? Faraway?
He dealt with electrochemistry.
Should we go with Morse code?
There's nothing else.
We don't have a different answer.
- Morse code...
- It does sound too obvious.
- sounds too obvious.
- Right.
Should we go with the Faraway signal?
The picture on top.
Isn't it really Morse code?
Let's go with Morse code.
Morse code.
I think it's simply just Morse code.
We will go with the Faraway signal.
That is incorrect.
What if it's Morse code?
- Shall we move on?
- Let's move on.
- Please don't be Morse code.
- Here's the answer.
Please!
- That is correct.
- That's right!
That's right!
- I said it from the start.
- Nice!
We thought too deeply.
- We shouldn't think too deeply.
- Right. We thought too deeply.
- This was a freebie.
- Right.
It was a freebie.
The questions earlier were hard.
"The leader is going to change tomorrow."
I think there will be a leader change.
There's nothing we can do.
Let's get the last question right.
Here's the last question.
"Official signatures
of country representatives?"
Isn't that "war with Japan?"
Supreme Commander for the Allied Powers.
That represents the allied countries.
Couldn't that be
the end of war declaration?
- "Geneva Conventions."
- Right.
- It's along those lines.
What were the Geneva Conventions again?
So what is the name of that?
An end-of-war agreement?
Isn't it a surrender?
A document of surrender?
- Whatever. Geneva Conventions.
- Go for it.
End of war declaration.
We will go with
Japan's written oath of surrender.
That is correct.
Gosh, that's a relief.
Japanese Instrument of Surrender.
- Instrument of Surrender?
The word "surrender" has to be included.
That was to announce the end of the war.
It's different from surrendering.
Instrument of Surrender? That was it?
Let's go.
I feel like an airhead.
- Don't say that.
- The leaders of each group...
should head to the Community Center...
- to collect the resources won.
- Great work.
Great work.
- See you.
- I'll be back.
Please collect the resources produced...
by Team White.
- Please collect the resources produced...
- Thank you.
by Team Blue.
Team Red can select
the type of credit to produce.
(Team Red credit selection)
(Before production)
However, if Team Red chooses to produce
pollution-free credits...
What are pollution-free credits?
Two pollution-free credits are provided
with one correct answer.
There's environmental pollution.
The decision between regular credits
and pollution-free credits...
can be made at the Community Center...
when collecting the resources...
- after the production session is over.
- Let's answer the questions first.
If you select regular credits,
you get 3 credits for 1 question.
If you select pollution-free credits,
you get 2 credits for 1 question.
(Pollution-free credits have
a lower production efficiency.)
Whenever regular credits are used,
pollution occurs.
The pollution level goes up
when regular credits are used.
Pollution-free credits
do not cause pollution.
When the pollution level is high,
a huge damage might occur...
against the safety and assets
of the Community Town residents.
I thought this was great for us.
It's a new type of credit.
I didn't find much meaning
with the credits yesterday.
(Credits weren't seen
to be valuable yesterday.)
With pollution-free credits,
I believe we can change minds
and turn things around.
- If we use regular credits,
- Yes?
all of our assets...
can be harmed.
That means we should use
pollution-free credits.
But let's say
we used pollution-free credits...
- and did well to protect the environment.
- Right.
If the other teams cause pollution...
- Right. All of us will get harmed.
- Right.
I don't see the need to use
pollution-free credits if that's the case.
But this is what it's like.
If we start producing
pollution-free credits from now on,
we will be able to delay future harm
against our safety.
Should we go for pollution-free credits
since we've earned a lot?
That could be good.
We'll choose pollution-free credits.
You have chosen pollution-free credits.
Please collect the resources produced
by Team Red.
The pollution-free credits have holes.
There are holes in these credits.
(Resources After Day 2's Production)
(Team White:
90 diamonds, 10 lives, 6 credits)
(Team Blue: 60 diamonds, 21 lives,
5 credits)
(Team Red:
50 diamonds, 6 lives, 29 credits)
Would Black know
about the pollution level?
We got something.
There's something in the mailbox.
What?
(A new rule card arrives at the dorm.)
We got something. Awesome.
We got something.
- Shall we take a look?
- I'm scared.
- Gosh! I'm scared!
- Is it going to say Black got it right?
Couldn't it be a death sentence
from Black?
"Black has already figured it out."
"You must make a purchase."
What if it says things like that?
Gosh, what is this?
Rules of war?
- It's scary.
- War? What?
Rules of war?
Rules of war. Gosh!
- War?
- This is insane. Rules of war.
War?
Rules of war, all of a sudden?
Well, we can never be peaceful.
- War?
- It's war.
- I hate war.
- So do I.
- We won't be left alone.
- We must go to war.
Here are the rules of war.
(Rules of war)
- A group that fails to earn...
- "A group that fails to earn..."
- resources through trade...
- "resources through trade..."
- will be able to declare war.
- "will be able to declare war."
Another group is chosen to be taken
to the battlefield...
for a group battle.
The winning group will be able to earn...
half of all of
the losing group's resources.
- Really?
- Half of all of the resources?
- Half of all of the resources.
- Awesome.
We'll go to war if things don't work out.
- It's a true war.
- Right.
"Half of all of the resources?"
My stomach hurts right now.
I'm not lying. My stomach hurts.
Once we lose,
- Gosh! My stomach hurts!
- that's the end of us.
We're definitely going to go to war.
This is the start of survival.
It's an attempt to shake everyone up.
"This is bad."
The seed of fear
started to grow inside of everyone.
"A bolt out of the blue."
"I want to die."
"Stress."
"A sudden rush of pressure."
"This is exciting."
"We're going all in."
It was inevitable.
Once the rules of war were announced,
there will be something
that forces us to go to war.
I thought that we had to be
prepared for that.
When a group wishes to go to war,
the leader must visit the Community Center
during the trade activity session,
declare war, and pay the fee for war.
The fee for war will be announced
by the number of diamonds every day.
It will be deducted from
the total prize money...
based on the value of diamonds
of that day.
It's deducted from the prize money.
- It's from our own money.
- It's deducted.
If we go to war,
that will cut down the 200,000 dollars.
There are 200 diamonds.
Let's say the fee costs 20 diamonds.
That's 20,000 dollars, as it's a 10th.
That will cut down the prize money
to 180,000 dollars.
This is for Team White.
Right. They will surely target us.
Definitely.
A declaration of war cannot be canceled.
Once war is declared,
all trade activities will stop.
Community Town will enter a state of war.
It's inevitable once it gets declared.
- Right. It's war right away.
- Right.
It's a state of war right away.
This is harsh.
Before the announcement
to the battlefield is made,
the following war activities may proceed.
Number one, forming an alliance.
The group in battle
can form an alliance with another group.
The allied group can enter the battle.
The spoils of war are based
on the initial group of war,
but when there's an allied group,
the spoils can be shared
or paid off together.
However, Team Black cannot participate
in the war...
or form an alliance.
Will they share the risk as well?
Right. It must be like that.
- If White goes against us,
- White goes against us,
- and we must persuade Red.
- we must persuade Red.
The number of members might influence
the war.
Is it better to have more numbers?
The numbers will be the same
if they form an alliance.
- Number two, weapon purchase.
- There are weapons as well?
During a state of war,
you may purchase weapons
at the Community Center.
There are three types of weapons.
They differ in price
based on their grades.
They are stronger when higher in price.
There is one weapon in each grade,
and there is no purchase limit
for each group.
They have no risks in declaring war.
They can issue more anyway.
They will surely declare war.
When purchasing a weapon, it will get
deducted from the prize money...
based on the value of diamonds
of that day.
Why does it keep getting deducted?
This was from the Community Center.
This is a fun society.
War?
When lives become rare,
- war will be inevitable.
- Right.
It's a matter of us surviving
or them surviving.
- Right. We must go after each other.
- Right.
- When we fail to secure six lives,
we have to go to war.
- That becomes the leverage for war.
- Right.
We have to go to war
or give up on someone.
- We have to give up on one member.
- Right.
It's a bet.
We were the villains.
This is bad.
We said Team White was the villain.
Why not go to war?
We'll all die if we don't survive.
That can't be helped.
We could hold hands
and head home together.
Right. We'll all die.
They must want us to have fewer members.
- They'll think that way.
- Right.
- The six of us surviving...
only benefits us.
- This is bad.
- It won't benefit them at all.
"The six of us must survive..."
"before we kill you first."
- We'll end up saying that.
- Right.
"If we don't secure our lives,"
- "we'll go to war."
- Right.
"It's more exciting
when we fight as a group of six."
The ones who kept going on about peace
until this morning...
changed after hearing about war.
"We should go to war!"
Luna looked excited.
She's already at the top.
"Just burn our money."
Saying those things with a smile
felt scary.
This is what's scary about people.
As soon as those rules were announced,
we went, "Sure. Let's battle it out
if things don't work out."
Seeing us say that naturally...
gave me goosebumps.
It's better to fight
if we are short on lives.
We'll get eliminated anyway.
I expected that moment to come.
But that has to be delayed
as much as possible.
The most important part is the fee of war.
I expect it to be really expensive.
I believe it will become
more expensive over time.
Once it starts,
war will be inevitable.
The sound of the first gunshots...
must be delayed as much as possible
for the best of all of us.
War will break out, no matter what.
But I don't plan to make it happen soon.
War causes harm anyway.
But when that moment comes,
we can be the ones to pull the trigger.
If it's going to happen anyway,
we have a higher chance...
of being at an advantage.
That will bring up
our chance of winning as well.
This was my calculation.
Don't threaten Team White too much.
They have a lot of diamonds...
and they can purchase weapons
and declare war.
"If you don't give us lives,"
"we have no choice but to declare war."
It's easier for them to declare war.
Right. War is easier for them.
They have the money and numbers.
They're thugs.
This team, Team Blue, is in danger...
because they have the lives.
If Team Blue doesn't sell the lives,
- If they don't sell them...
- we will ally with Team White.
- Right.
- "Let's wipe out Team Blue."
If we go, "Let's wipe them out..."
This is a rule for Team White.
Money and numbers are needed for war.
Team Blue always acted high-handedly...
as they knew they were
in a dominant position.
They acted like that
to bring out better deals.
But that kind of behavior
can be punished now.
That can be a spark of war.
Finally,
there was a way to stop
Team Blue's threats with their lives.
If Team Blue continues to
keep the lives to themselves,
there's a great way to threaten them.
I believe this is great for us.
Team Blue will end up becoming
the opponents.
Right.
Will half of what they have be taken?
That's crazy.
- Right.
- It's a revolution if we win today.
That's 11 lives.
That means we would be able to survive
until the end.
That's why war sounds like a good idea.
It's important to have
a good cause for war.
- If we start a war without a cause,
- Right.
they will definitely form an alliance.
If they ally with Team White,
we have no chance of winning.
What if we are to persuade Team White?
"We'll give you all of our credits."
- No. We need lives.
- Right.
We have to ally with them
because of their lives.
We should ask about
how many they are willing to trade off.
"How many do you want?"
"How many can you sell?"
"We won't sell any."
"Really? Then, we go to war."
But...
I'm not sure. This might be because
I'm a pacifist.
War must not break out.
If war breaks out,
our prize money gets deducted.
- That's what it's like in real life.
- Right.
Except for the benefit
of the ones who start war,
it's a constant destruction...
of everything else.
This is a red flag for us.
But if Team White doesn't want to
go to war,
they would want 6 lives.
We can't give out 6 lives.
We're stacked with lives right now.
If we threaten the ones
with their survival,
- they will start a war.
- They will start a war.
"If you care only about your safety,"
"the ones who are fighting to survive
will bite."
The ones who are fighting to survive
always cause a revolt.
They will start a war
if they are about to die.
Right.
But if we win...
That will be huge.
If we win,
we are...
- Shall we just...
- Gosh.
We might end up
starting a war at this rate.
She's going to start a war.
"Let's start a war."
What if we win?
Right.
- Then it's totally...
- Right.
Then we can get it done
without lifting a finger.
Or...
- This is so stressful. It's crazy.
- Look.
We could contact the White first.
If this war is unavoidable,
and we must win,
how about we start it first?
Because we can definitely beat
nine people.
Think about it.
Then we can wipe off Team Credit.
You know what I mean?
If we wipe them off,
we get to keep what they have.
Those credits...
- The credits...
- We can split them.
That way, we can earn more lives
with those credits.
Now that I think about it,
if anyone comes after us,
there aren't many people left
to earn lives.
We can take advantage of it.
We might as well...
attack them first.
We have to attack them once, at least.
We have to declare war, at least once.
It's unavoidable.
We can't help it due to the system.
We have to make an ally,
but if we form an alliance with them,
it's our loss.
So we might as well go talk to them first,
form an alliance,
and kill them all.
- Then...
- I like that.
the chance of us losing the war
is unlikely.
We get to earn more credits...
to buy lives,
and we can all survive.
We should persuade them
and form an alliance.
That is our only option. Look.
We have to get into action.
I didn't realize that we were cornered.
I thought we were safe after today,
but we're not.
This can't wait.
We have to get this done before today.
We have to declare war even tomorrow.
She's different from yesterday.
She's a different person today.
- Did she change while sleeping?
- She seems possessed.
What do you think?
You know what I mean, right?
We need to contact them as soon as we can.
- Yes.
- It's all about timing.
We have to do it as soon as we can.
If I got this right,
do you want to declare war today?
- No.
We have to talk to them today...
- and declare war tomorrow.
- She wants to...
win Team White over today...
and declare war tomorrow.
I think this is a very good idea.
But we need to think...
if getting rid of Team Red...
will only benefit us.
Of course not.
But if we agree...
not to declare war in the end,
then it works for us.
But that's not the case,
and we should prepare for that.
- This is so tough.
- We're talking about it even now.
We're worried about the team splitting up.
- Of course.
- The chance of us...
becoming a majority is
either now or never.
Still, we can keep the team safe this way.
Because this wipes out one team.
And the total number of lives we have...
can save nine people.
So if we team up with them,
we gain peace.
And that's done through a war.
In the end, a war is necessary
for our peace.
In the end, doing it today...
will get us allies at the lowest cost,
and it's the fastest way to gain peace.
Gosh.
In my opinion, I think we have...
enough number of lives.
I think...
it's enough to survive for four days.
We could increase the time...
to play the game together.
It's not just for them,
but I believe there's a gain...
from keeping society running.
But they're saying
we must secure what we have,
and that we must declare war.
We have completely different opinions,
so I don't even know...
where to start.
If I were to bring it up,
I don't know how to persuade them.
If there are three people,
it's split into 2 to 1.
And it seems I'm the one.
Because I'm a minority,
I was losing confidence in myself.
Maybe they're right.
I had a hard time...
because that didn't sound absurd.
To persuade them,
I needed to say something that excels
their ideas.
But it didn't work at all.
They wouldn't listen.
Is individual ability all we're taking
with us...
from this survival?
That thought kept occurring to me...
and made me dizzy.
(Writer Salt)
So...
I know it's funny. It's only a game.
So I'm...
I'm flustered right now...
by the fact that I'm crying.
From now on, you can use the supermarket.
Do you want to go to
the supermarket together?
- Sounds good.
- Sure.
I'm curious about the price range.
Me too. I'm hungry.
What's Team Black's strategy?
- They're away.
Vector is planning on something.
Now is the time.
- It's Vector.
- Hello.
It's open as soon as we're here.
Hi, Vector.
Hello.
How did your productive activities
go today?
- Productive activities? Not bad.
- Not bad?
You look like you're in a good mood.
I'm very happy.
- Really?
- Yes.
Did you get to do
any productive activities?
You got it.
What kind of productive activities
did you do?
I need to produce these supplies.
To add popular items,
I have to answer the questions.
Do you get physical rewards...
- for productive activities?
- That's right.
I have pork belly and Coke Zero.
If you want a lunchbox,
you can have a lunchbox.
What do you want for lunch?
- Well...
- I want something with rice.
Have you heard about the war?
- Yes.
You have to pay for all war supplies
with diamonds.
You'll be like the US.
We're not going to have a war.
I want to avoid a war...
- because a war means someone has to die.
- Right.
That means less share for me.
Why is it less?
Because there are fewer people eating.
It means less food consumption.
One of the things I wanted to
tell your team was,
to raise the value of your diamonds,
you need inflation.
I need to make the products expensive...
for people to want more diamonds.
There's nothing I can do
about the war cost...
because that's not my authority.
But I can change the price of the food.
In the end, they'll have to buy
at least one egg.
That will put you...
in a favorable position
during the negotiations.
We can't help but create inflation.
- Right.
- But the thing is,
we'd like to set the limit with you.
- In the end, it's all related.
- Right.
What I can tell you is,
without issuing the diamonds,
I'll pretend they've been issued...
and raise the price.
Are you saying we should fix the price?
Then it becomes intimidation.
We can get...
lives and credits for a low price...
by intimidating them.
It'd be great if it went as you planned.
But I'm afraid it might backfire.
- Like starting a war?
- Yes. What if they fight back...
or start a war to steal them?
Or they might go,
"We're not trading anymore."
If they boycott trading for a day or two,
we actually...
- We'll lose a lot of lives.
- need...
a lot of lives.
We can't face a hostile phase...
for a long time.
I wonder if that's a good idea
from the start.
Right.
Vector said,
"I'm destined to cooperate with you..."
"because if you control the money supply,"
"it affects the price of my items."
He said things like that.
To be honest,
the money supply is pointless for Vector.
He has the power to set the price.
He's not that affected by us.
Yet, he keeps saying...
he wants to cooperate with us.
I think he is...
an extraordinary man.
Anyway, he's well aware
of Team Black's money supply.
So we need to...
He's not an ordinary man,
but we still need to...
talk to him into it.
Our plan is to build trust at first.
Team Red is coming.
- But it's...
- Hello.
Is the store not open yet?
- It's open.
- It's open. Do you need anything?
- I'm not sure. Donkey's starving.
- Well...
- Let's take a look.
- We need to eat.
- Let's go.
- He's getting dizzy.
- It's closing.
- Here...
Do you have the price ready?
Not yet.
Today was too... One second.
Let me check the money supply.
Okay.
If Team White says...
- they need the credits...
- Be generous?
- Let's keep it cool.
- Okay.
Even if there's no benefit to us,
we should give them enough...
and ask them to support us...
if a war is declared.
But if they betray us,
- then...
- Right. We can't do that on credit.
we'll just blow up the bombs.
Then let's kill them all.
With our skills.
Wonderful.
What are they going to do about it?
How did the game go today?
- It was harder than expected.
- Hard?
I could tell.
We thought it was over faster
than expected.
- Really?
- Yes.
- You saw the war, right?
Let's keep it peaceful...
It's too complicated.
Let's not fight.
If you don't give us lives,
we have no choice but to declare war.
It's all about life in the end, right?
- Yes.
- Because the lives are limited.
We have the same goal then.
To win lives.
That's true.
- You're right.
- Yes.
This is getting complicated.
- Then we will...
- We'll take six lunchboxes...
for this much.
- Five in total?
- Five in total.
So one diamond per lunchbox?
Because 1 diamond equals to 1,000 dollars.
- Then here's what we'll do.
- Okay.
One diamond per lunchbox.
- One diamond per lunchbox?
- Yes.
For 6 ramyeon and 6 sodas,
give me 4 more, so 10 in total.
You can have it for breakfast tomorrow
or in the middle of the night.
We don't eat in the middle of the night.
- We don't do that. We're on a diet.
- We don't eat breakfast.
But I want ten diamonds.
But we don't need to stock up
on food right now.
And we're Team White.
And the number of diamonds...
doesn't really matter to you...
- Of course.
- right now.
It only matters...
when the currency value is adjusted.
Even this afternoon,
if we adjust it...
But you never know.
Anyway, all we need is six lunchboxes.
- You only want to eat six lunchboxes?
- We don't need...
Yes. We don't need any more negotiations.
Okay. Wait until tomorrow.
You never know
how things will change tomorrow.
- Enjoy your lunchboxes for today.
- Okay.
Make your payment.
What a waste.
One, two, three,
four, five, six.
Thank you.
- Give us more.
- What?
- Maybe ramyeon?
- Give us 1 or 2 ramyeon.
Maybe like small cups?
- You have to buy it.
- You're nice.
We'll keep the price...
a secret.
You can charge other people more.
- Anyway,
- Thank you for the food.
thank you for making the first payment.
Let's keep a good relationship.
(Next is Team Red.)
Does the price vary?
Yes. What would you like to buy?
Tell us the price for ramyeon.
I'll have one big Yukgaejang.
Why don't you get one lunchbox each?
Okay.
I didn't give them anything on the house,
but if you can keep it a secret
since you're men,
I'll give you one ramyeon each for free.
Are you buying this too?
- We'll get that too.
- Yes.
- We can eat that later.
- Okay.
Including those three...
You can take two eggs.
Two diamonds for that.
- So five in total?
- Yes.
- Are you okay with that?
- Five.
- If you could do that for us...
Thank you.
The use of diamonds finally feels real.
- Don't tell anyone about the price.
- Okay.
(Team Red's purchase with 5 diamonds)
- Thank you.
- Team White's order...
- has been delivered.
- Is it over there?
Over there?
- Enjoy.
- Thank you for the food.
- Thank you.
(Team White returns to their room
after receiving their food.)
- Enjoy your food.
- This is nice.
- The food looks good today.
- I think our food is here.
- Yes.
Vector, what are you having?
- I already ate. Yes.
- Did you?
By any chance,
do you know if...
the pollution level is added
to the resource monitoring?
Not yet.
If we can't check, that's not good.
Exactly.
Well...
I'll only tell you.
There's something called
the pollution credit.
Pollution?
We were using the pollution credit
until yesterday.
Starting today,
we got the pollution-free credit.
The pollution-free credit
must be more valuable.
It should be.
The thing is,
if we use the pollution credit,
and if it reaches a certain level,
- everyone's resource...
- Everyone's resource.
gets deleted.
If it's developed rapidly,
it creates air pollution...
- or environmental pollution.
- Right.
That'd cut the life in half.
Right. The life is likely to be affected.
- Because it's environmental pollution.
- Environmental pollution affects life.
Then today,
Team White and Team Red...
will form an alliance...
and kill Team Blue.
Get rid of their lives.
You can survive until tomorrow.
If there are no variables.
From what I've seen,
you shouldn't do anything.
- Instead of becoming a target?
- Yes.
Instead of starting a war.
Actually, if war is declared,
it's my loss.
- Because people have to pay diamonds.
- But...
if Team Blue doesn't sell, it's a war.
- Right.
- Yes. So...
- I'll persuade Team Blue...
- Right.
- If Team Blue doesn't sell...
- They won't be so ruthless.
- to keep it peaceful.
- Yes.
- I'll carry this.
- Let's go.
- See you later.
- Bye.
I'm still neutral.
I'll talk to them to maintain peace.
Is Team Blue skipping lunch?
Why aren't they here?
I talked to them before.
They're not interested in food.
I think they're trying to endure it today.
That's crazy.
Team Black...
He knows everyone's information.
We need to buy him
to stop him from leaking our information.
We should be ready...
to give them one of our lives today.
For sure.
If we sell a day's worth,
- we can sell three lives.
- Yes.
We can sell 2 and 1.
By 2 and 1, who are you referring to?
- Two to Team White,
- and one to Vector.
Because we need to win Team Black over.
Do you want to meet Vector first
to be safe?
Because that will save us time.
Right.
- We can only give him one.
- But...
we need to think about
what percentage we're going to ask for.
Twenty percent from a day.
(Team Blue wants a percentage of
the market sales in return for a life.)
Even 20 percent is...
- We're making a concession big time.
- not much for what we're giving.
Honestly, I think...
instead of asking a percentage
of the sales,
we should build a friendship...
- and receive food.
- We can just...
Receive food?
You say this
because you're full right now.
But when you're hungry...
and struggling for real...
I don't mind starving for real.
Money means more to me.
- So...
- I prefer money too.
I have no intention of paying
1,000 dollars for it.
I actually don't plan to spend it at all.
Then instead of a percentage,
we could just demand a set amount.
Is this lunchtime?
It's lunchtime right now.
Do you want to go check it out?
- Let's go check it out.
- Let's pretend...
we're checking it out
because we're hungry.
Is Team Blue not eating?
Hi.
- Store owner.
- Vector.
- Hello.
- How's your business going today?
- It's going pretty well.
- Good?
How much are you charging?
Are you here to shake me down?
We're here to make an agreement.
- You are pretty scary.
- No.
- We...
- You look like thugs.
You threatened me with my life.
What did you do for
the productive activities this morning?
I added items here.
- Do you have to solve questions?
- So I got Coke Zero.
- Really?
- I have three packs of pork belly.
- Coke Zero?
I see it.
My goodness.
- He's clearly smart.
- He's smart.
How's the price range?
Each team paid ten.
- Ten diamonds?
- Yes.
I was actually thinking...
about taking half
of your expected sales today.
If you only got ten from each team,
we need ten at least.
That's ridiculous...
because we got 10 diamonds
for 1 life yesterday from Team White.
It should be way more expensive.
- Life's worth more than that now.
- But he hasn't...
made much yet...
- But...
- It's too much for him.
I'll show you how much I've made so far.
I didn't do anything...
This is a life.
We're trading it for a day.
I'll come clean.
This is awesome.
- I didn't see you coming.
- Okay.
This is all I have. I only have 11.
This is not easy.
- I feel...
- Okay.
At this rate,
instead of taking them,
it's better to go with a percentage.
- For the future.
- But I think...
food is a good idea too.
Because the food price will go up.
- We have to choose one.
- I think the food is only right.
Keep in mind that we can't take a lot,
and it could be worth nothing.
- Those diamonds.
- Right. They might become worthless.
Right. That's true.
If...
you give me a life,
I'll serve you nicely.
I think we should trust him on that.
- Right.
- Let's trust each other.
- Bring me a life.
- Okay.
While you're here,
why don't you take some items?
- Okay. We...
- What would you like to eat?
I want to take a lot.
First, we need soy milk.
- We need the tofu chips.
- The tofu chips.
We need the tofu chips.
This is my favorite.
Are we having one Coke Zero each?
Take two eggs?
- Take two eggs.
- The eggs.
That's worth 20 diamonds.
Let's take one more pizza.
You don't have a microwave.
Let's save it here then.
Let's call it a deal.
We must not get caught.
No wonder I wanted to wear something big.
Feel free to take it.
You'll be fine.
- Enjoy.
- Thank you.
- Make sure to give me a life.
- For sure.
Promise.
In a way, I tried
some black-market trading.
My supermarket was written
as Black Market.
And what is Black Market?
It's for illegal trading.
So...
I lived up to my name.
I don't know how it'll turn out,
but I tried making a deal outside the law.
It's worth 1,000 dollars.
- It looks good.
- Thank you for the food.
- Thank you.
Enjoy.
Before the price goes up at night,
should we stock up on the food?
Actually, I was thinking
it wouldn't be so bad...
to get a few things for ten diamonds.
But the currency is way too valuable
right now.
At this rate, all the diamonds...
will end up in Team Black's hands.
That's true.
So we'll end up issuing...
more and more...
to keep the balance.
That will make the price go up.
That means more for Team Black.
Then we'll end up starving.
I remember, "Increase the money supply..."
from yesterday. And even today,
he kept telling us to induce inflation.
The two things he said keep bothering me.
- I thought that was strange.
- It was fishy.
What is Team Black thinking?
(Dormitory for Team Black)
I'll go solve it.
Okay. I got it.
I'll say that it has nothing to do...
with the amount of petroleum reserves.
(No.)
It's wrong.
Please pick up a new answer sheet.
I know it isn't,
but I'll say it is.
(Yes.)
I have to answer it
to turn things in my favor.
It's wrong.
(Vector tries to answer
the technique development questions.)
I'll bring the answers.
Goodbye.
The trading for Day Two will begin.
The residents may ring the bell
in the living room...
to request another group a meeting.
Is Team White there?
- Let's ask for the best.
- Yes.
Team White?
I'd like to meet Team White
in the Town Hall.
Team Blue asked Team White...
Team Blue asked Team White.
The request granted.
Sounds good.
(The request has been granted.)
Do we wait in the Town Hall?
- Do you want to wait there?
- Yes.
You may declare war...
during the trading hours starting today.
Any leaders who want to declare war...
must pay for the war cost
at the Community Center...
and declare war.
The war cost today is...
How much does it cost?
- Exactly.
- I'm curious.
They're going to tell us the war cost.
The cost of starting a war today
is 15 diamonds.
- What? That's way too cheap.
- It barely costs anything.
- That's it?
Only 15 diamonds to start a war?
That's pretty cheap.
- It doesn't cost a lot.
- Which means every group can go for it.
The cost of starting a war
was way too low.
Think about it.
We were willing to pay eight diamonds...
just to have dinner.
But only 15 diamonds?
That's way too cheap.
If war costs are too low,
people will declare war recklessly.
It's probably the cheapest today.
Should we do it today?
Starting a war is inevitable.
If it's something we must do
at least once,
we might as well strike early.
That's where I stand now.
We could potentially take 11 lives...
by only investing 15 diamonds.
That's pretty good.
It's an amazing deal.
It won't be 15 diamonds tomorrow.
- Probably not.
- Just today.
- Just today, right?
- Fifteen diamonds for today.
So that's 15,000 dollars
out of 200,000 dollars.
A lot of people commented that
the cost of starting a war was too low.
But I think it's reasonably priced...
because wars will keep on happening.
That's 15,000 dollars.
That's not a small amount.
That's enough to buy a car.
This concludes the announcement
from the Community Center.
What kind of Community Center is this?
It's trying to drive a wedge
in the community.
War? Okay.
(30 minutes ago)
Hold on.
The cost of starting a war...
(War Cost Determination)
Fifteen diamonds.
The cost of war has been set.
Please determine the cost of the weapon.
I'll encourage them to start a war.
They'll pick their weapon...
after declaring war.
So weapons should be priced high.
I'll set 30 diamonds for A,
20 diamonds for B, and 10 diamonds for C.
The costs of weapons have been set.
Here's what I'd like to try here.
In this community,
rules are set,
and there's this condition
that we're all playing a game.
I'd like to betray people...
and harm others.
I also want to spread rumors
and throw things into chaos.
I can try this just for ten days.
It's going to be so fun.
(Resident Registration on Day 1)
Your color is Black.
There's only one resident in your group.
By default, you're the leader.
Team Black will act as a merchant
in the Community Town.
- A merchant?
- The merchant decides...
the prices of the items
sold at the supermarket.
The diamonds acquired through sales
will be the merchant's prize.
However,
you have a hidden role, Vector.
What is it?
Please read the following command,
and you'll find out your real role.
What is it? Say what?
(Command)
"The truth of the weapon dealer..."
"placed within secret room of center."
This is it, right? Gosh, no way.
My gosh.
Goodness, this is crazy.
"A weapon dealer?"
(The Rules for the Weapon Dealer)
Oh, my.
You're a weapon dealer
of the Community House.
The residents believe that
your prize money will come...
from the sales at the supermarket.
The weapon dealer's prize money
will solely come...
from the war costs and weapon sales.
"More wars yield bigger prize money."
I have to turn them against each other.
It's on the house. Help yourselves.
Tell me which one you want.
You can choose from this selection.
(He provided the food for free
from the first day.)
(The weapon dealer can't take the sales
from the supermarket.)
On the surface,
I want to keep playing
the generous supermarket owner.
But there may come a moment
where things change rather drastically.
It will be when wars keep happening...
and the diamonds become more valuable.
The weapon dealer can check
each group's total resources.
They got two more.
The weapon dealer can monitor...
and wiretap each group's living room.
No one built up a good rapport
better than Vector yesterday.
- He did a great job with that.
- Yes.
He went around
and talked to every single group.
(A wiretapping device is hidden
in the living room.)
Acting in good faith is very important.
The longer this goes on,
having a good rapport...
I acquired several important clues.
For instance, I got to hear
their honest thoughts.
If a war breaks out,
so many people will get eliminated.
- Right.
- Yes.
Is it a good idea to start a war...
until that happens?
Every team is suspicious of me.
I don't think Vector will have to use...
- the diamonds to get the supplies.
- Right.
Collecting as many diamonds as possible...
That sounds one-dimensional.
I'm sure there's something else
underneath that.
Team Red is suspecting me the most.
That was so nerve-racking.
Once they open the door and walk in,
they can see that
I'm listening to their conversations.
And there was a card
for the weapon dealer.
So I took it off.
Either way, I have to use the room...
during the break
or while the snack bar is open.
When I'm wearing the headset,
I might suddenly hear a voice.
Then I need to listen to that.
So I take it off for a bit.
The Town Hall is open.
So anyone can walk in at any time.
I need to turn off the TV.
My position isn't all exciting,
which I thought it would be at first.
Were you productive?
Yes, I was.
What were you able to produce?
I had to produce these supplies.
- So you get actual goods in return?
- That's right.
I got pork belly and Coke Zero.
I made up a bunch of lies.
"I got these supplies
through my productive activity."
"I'm working hard for our community."
I wanted to emphasize that,
so I made up a productive activity...
I didn't even do and shared it.
Moreover, there are puzzles...
in the residents' dormitories that
reveal the identity of the weapon dealer.
- What are those numbers for?
- If all the residents...
- put together their information...
- Three, five, one...
- and solve all the puzzles...
- Two, four,
one, four.
Add three to the sixth power to that.
Two hundred and five. Who's good at math?
- Are you good at math?
- No.
Then the weapon dealer's secret safe
will be exposed.
The military funds collected
up to that point will be wiped out.
"The answer to the puzzle is the command
you speak to enter the room."
I'm glad I wrote that down.
"The truth of the weapon dealer
placed within secret room..."
"Secret room of center." That's here.
The weapon dealer has an ally
who has disguised...
as a resident.
Hold on.
The ally can only receive
half of the weapon dealer's prize money.
When the ally gets eliminated,
the weapon dealer's final prize money
will be halved.
I have to protect the ally,
no matter what.
"In war, what is sacrificed first?"
The one who asks you this question...
is your ally.
Your answer to the question is "Truth."
That's your secret contact code.
Use your ally to cause conflicts
in the groups.
(Use your ally to cause conflicts
in the groups.)
"Placed within secret room of center."
"Secret room of center."
I need to stop them
from solving the puzzles.
I wonder if I can pull this off.
- Wait. Is it "secret room of center?"
- Three.
Is there a secret room in the Center?
In the Community Center?
Can't we go to the Center now?
Now?
Is it "secret room of center?"
I noticed a code in the dormitory.
Anyone would've found that suspicious.
I wanted to solve it fast.
There were six numbers.
I can group them by three.
And there are 18 of them.
I followed this order. Then I got...
I had 6 fragments of 3 letters.
I thought following the order
would give me a sentence.
So the phrase we got was
"secret room of center."
We need to find it fast.
We need to find it really fast.
There's something we have to take care of.
I'm so curious.
The curiosity is killing me.
What's that thing on the right?
It looks suspicious, right?
(Team Red searched through the Center
from Day One.)
Is that the place?
We must hurry.
(Day 1, evening)
Clearly, this looks very suspicious.
It won't rotate, right?
(Day 1, dawn)
It's closed.
- It's over for the day.
- It's closed.
It made me wonder
if the code was in other rooms too.
So I asked around.
Did you guys solve the code on the wall?
We didn't get to that yet.
- You didn't?
- No.
- Wasn't there...
- Yes?
extra information on the wall?
Extra information?
I didn't get a chance to look around.
I should hurry. I'm going to solve it.
My honey jar.
One, two, three.
How do I open this?
The only center in our town...
is the Community Center.
I kept looking.
But there was no secret room.
I didn't see anything
resembling a secret room.
I need to stop them
from solving the puzzles.
I wanted to solve it fast.
(The one trying to keep it hidden,
the one trying to find it)
(The Community 2: Invisible Hand)